Guide to the Margaret McFadden Papers, 1825-2013 RL.00872
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Addition (2015-0095), 1825-2010; 20 boxes
  - Fem Theory - presentation - NWSA, 1982-1983 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - M's application, 1984 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Ms. for WS International Forum, 1984 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - MM's personal file, 1982 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Integrating women into curric, 1986 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Schlesinger, 1983 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Fellowship app - MM, 1984-1985 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Methodist church women's history, 1984 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Valedictorian speech by Kate Eldridge, Washington, Iowa, 1910 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - SEWSA - nomination for Kim Hall, 2015 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - MM remarks & photo - re Pat Beavre + 4 Tenants of Feminism, 2013-2014 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - SEWSA - prop. of founding mother (MM) & papers from Richard Taylor of SEWSA, 2014 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Miscellaneous items, undated (Box 6, Folder 15, 16)
  - International Congress on Women, Trinity College, Dublin, 1987 (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - Dual Career Partnerships: A Bibliography, 1986 (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Mill Girls - Rev. for Albion, 2003 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Finland - Sweden, 2001 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Maine - Web of Women's Friendships Conference, 2002 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Women and Politics, University of Southern Maine, 2002 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Societa Italiana Delle Storiche, Terza Congresso, 2003 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Mexico, 2002 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Travelers in Latin America, Mexico, 2002 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Revisions (2) W - Poland paper, 2001 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Berks - Finland proposal, 2002 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - SEWSA, 1991 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - BRICHA Proposal, 2001-2002 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - US-USSR Bridges for Peace, 1988-1989 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - US-USSR Bridges for Peace 4th Women's Exchange & miscellaneous items, 1989 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Bridges for Peace, 1989 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Emails, memorandums, brochures, various academic papers/correspondence, 2002-2009 (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - Additional US-USSR Bridges for Peace materials, 1988-1989 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Mutual Educational Exchange Grant Authorization, 2003 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Alice Paul CD, notes, thank-you cards, miscellaneous, 2001-2009 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Reports cards & miscellaneous school papers, 1949-1959 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Overhead transparencies, undated (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Lesbian Literature - notes & syllabi, 1979-1980 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Women & Russia articles, 1984-1989 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Engels, The Origin of the Family diagram, undated (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Women in E. Germany, 1993 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Clara Zetkin, 1976 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Anna Ruling - 1904 - On Homosexuality (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - "What It Means to Love Another Woman", undated (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - "What is Heterosexuality and What Causes It?", 1984 (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Feminist Critical Theory diagram, undated (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Feminist Theories, 1989 (Box 8, Folder 15, 16)
  - Miscellaneous papers, 1962-1989 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Copies of various newspapers, 1977-1988 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Book proposal on Early 19th Century Comparative Feminist Theory, undated (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - 9 Old Comic Books (Including 3 Wonder Woman and 2 in Swedish), undated (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - High school graduation speech and papers, 1959 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - School awards and ribbons, 1951-1958 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - School composition books & miscellaneous papers, undated (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Black & white photos and photo slides, undated (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Various App. State-related papers, 2000-2012 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Honors society papers, 1995-1997 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Received letters, 1995-1996 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - The Woman Question, 1988 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Ida B. Wells-Barnett, undated (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Witchcraft lecture, 1999 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Witchcraft - transparencies, undated (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Hildegard of Bingen, undated (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Herstorical documents, undated (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - "Why Witches Were Women", undated (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Overhead maps & handouts, undated (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Women's History Workshop with Joan Scott, 2008 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Transatlantic Feminism Ict. - Finland, 2001 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Estonia, 2000 (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - Application for docentship & other papers, 2000 (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - BRICHA, 2001 (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - Reel Food paper, 2002 (Box 10, Folder 14b)
  - Babette's Feast, 2002-2003 (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - Chocolat, 2002 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Like Water for Chocolate, 2002 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Feminist Theory and Women of Color, 1991 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Notepads with miscellaneous notes, undated (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Between Wars Conference, Warsaw/Obory, 2000 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Teaching materials from Appalachian State and other institutions, 1997-2005 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Finland/NY: Pictures, postcards, & miscellaneous, 2000 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Women in Journalism stamps, flower + Canning awards, and postcard, 2001 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Publications by the Uganda Land Alliance, 2002 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Gendered Worlds: Gains and Challenges, 2002 (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Copy of The New Vision, 2002 (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - OM - Water, Food, Sex, Violence, 2003 (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - Food, Water, Sex, & Violence, 2002 (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - UNCSW, 2006 (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - NGO Committee on the Status of Women, 2006 (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - Photos: Anglican Consultative Council ECUSA Delegates and Provincial Delegates, 2006 (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - Anglican Women's Empowerment, 2005-2006 (Box 11, Folder 17)
  - UN Commission on the Status of Women, 2006 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Miscellaneous papers, 2010-2011 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Not For Ourselves Alone - Stanton-Anthony, 2002 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Not For Ourselves Alone faculty guide summary, 1994-2009 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Virginia Woolf & Three Guineas, 1990-2003 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Virginia Woolf: Room, Three, Modernism, & WWI, 1992-1994 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Fem diagram & synthesis charts, 2005-2009 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Richard T. Barker Friends of the Library Award - App. State, 2004-2005 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Untitled photos & negatives, 1989 (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Russia pix/pictures from USSR trip, 1989 (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Postcards from Russia, undated (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Photo slides from Russia, 1988 (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - Russian For Citizen Diplomats cassette tape, undated (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - Photos: Nordic Women's Hist. Conf. in Finland & Maggie with Historian Gerda Lerner U of Wisconsin-Madison, 1983-1994 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Russian souvenir, undated (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Indivisible postcard set, 1999 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Book published in Russian, 1988 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Course files: Abo Akademi University, 2005 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - LGBTQ stickers and advertisements, undated (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - NWSAJ files & other miscellaneous items, undated (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Women of Eureka booklet, 1995 (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Two notepads with handwritten notes, undated (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - Photocopy of Australia from a Woman's Point of View & notes, undated (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - Letter, thank-you card, article on radical feminism, & other miscellaneous papers, 1994-2009 (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - Copies of various newspapers, 1995-2002 (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - Project Summary, International Studies Scholarly Travel Grant, 1995 (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - A Feminist Perspective on Population Control - Third National Immigration & Population Outlook Conference, 1995
  - Report of URC grant, 1995-1996 (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - Memorandum: Australia research trip, 1996 (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - Card and decorated fabric squares from Uganda, undated (Box 13, Folder 17)
  - Votes for Women playing cards, undated (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Pamphelts on domestic violence, sexual assault, & reproductive rights, undated (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Floppy disks: NWSA and WMST syllabus information, undated (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - MM ASU office backup CD, undated (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Photo slides: Uganda and Kenya, undated (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Transcript of emails regarding Australia trip, 1996 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Retirement cards & luncheon program, 2009 (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Miscellaneous cards & postcards, 2002-2014 (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - Women Who Dared postcards, undated (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - Marquis Who's Who in America letter, 2010 (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - Tin skeleton & brochure, undated (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - Miscellaneous LGBTQ-related materials, 2007 (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - Sallie Bingham Center 4th Biennial Symposium program & card, 2009 (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - Photocopy of The Female Advocate + photocopy of miscellaneous book covers, undated (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Tendencies in the Women's Liberation Movement charts, undated (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - US-USSR Bridges for Peace questionnaire, 1989 (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - British women writers, undated (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Ireland, 1987 (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Winston-Salem Journal clipping sent to parents, 1989 (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Photocopy order from Schlesinger Library, Radcliffe College, 1984 (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - Fem. Theory file, undated (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Anatomy of Difference + other articles by MM, undated (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - 7th Berks. on Hist. of Women - Wellesley, 1987 (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - Fem Theory Diagram & Synthesis charts, undated (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - Typed pages - story of Glenora McFadden, undated (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - Newspaper clippings from high school, 1958 (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - School assignments & drawings, 1950 (Box 15, Folder 14)
  - Adjucators' comment sheets, 1956 (Box 15, Folder 15)
  - Photocopies: Literature on women's solo travel, undated (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - School drawings, undated (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Miscellaneous photocopies pages, undated (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - From Flag to Flag photocopy, undated (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Mary Grew's diary (1840) - photocopy, undated (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Uganda Land Alliance poster, undated (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - Salem - Walker & Dillard, undated (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Photocopy of The Female Advocate (1799), undated (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - Photocopy of handwritten document, undated (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - Fem Theory diagram & synthesis charts, undated (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - Pat Beaver's retirement talk, 2013 (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - Photocopy of For the Liberator: Letter to Mrs. Davis (Oct. 26, 1850), undated (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - Photocopy order: Columbia University Rare Book and Manuscript Library, 2000 (Box 16, Folder 13)
  - Photocopy from Schlesinger Library, undated (Box 16, Folder 14)
  - Segments from map of Ireland, undated (Box 16, Folder 15)
  - Photocopy of handwritten document, undated (Box 16, Folder 16)
  - Soviet woman, 1989 (Box 16, Folder 17)
  - Poster: 3rd International Interdisciplinary Congress on Women, 1987 (Box 16, Folder 18)
  - Photocopies from Records of Fritz Anneke and Mathilda Franziska, undated (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Contributions to American Women Writers, 1980 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Photocopy of the New York Tribune (June 29-July 7, 1863), undated (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Photocopy of New York TImes (July 4, 1863), undated (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Photocopy: Handwritten document, undated (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Baby clothes worn by grandfather - shirt, 1885 (Box 18)
  - Baby clothes worn by grandfather - hats, 1885 (Box 19)
  - Equality Barbie, 2010 (Box 20)
- Addition (2016-0028), 1960s-2015
  - Fairfield, Dec 3-9, 2013 (Box 1)
  - Memo of agreement-MM to HLST, 2008 (Box 1)
  - New economy symposium education presentation, Apr 2013 (Box 1)
  - Writing week-Trinity Center, May 2009 (Box 1)
  - Amsterdam-maps and IFRWH program, 2010 (Box 1)
  - Salem book review, 2009 (Box 1)
  - ICD Program-Berlin, Jan 2012 (Box 1)
  - Berlin-Inst for Cult Diplomacy and correspondence, May-June 2012 (Box 1)
  - Pakistan Fulbright, Nov 2011 (Box 1)
  - Mexico, Mar 2010 (Box 1)
  - NY Loft Appl., 2006 (Box 1)
  - Joni Seager, Feb-Mar 2011 (Box 1)
  - A women should never be seen eating-overheads, Feb 2002 (Box 1)
  - Gender and food symposium, 2010 (Box 1)
  - Queer London conference, Mar 2013 (Box 1)
  - London, Mar 2013 (Box 1)
  - David McGurn on MDG's, undated (Box 1)
  - Lydia Sklevicky articles and Yugoslavia, undated (Box 1)
  - London and LSE maps, Sept 2009 (Box 1)
  - SEWSA papers: eating, reading, writing women, Mar 2010 (Box 1)
  - Response: the voice of women in mission, Mar 2005 (Box 1)
  - Pro-seminar: women and food, Summer 2004 (Box 1)
  - Oxford round table: women and education, Mar 2013 (Box 1)
  - Aletta: Institute for women's history, 2010 (Box 1)
  - 18th Annual conference of the women's history network, Sept 2009 (Box 1)
  - The making of a feminist, 1989 (Box 1)
  - Feminist Theory Bibliography, 1980s (Box 1)
  - Women's studies coordinator, 1996-1997 (Box 1)
  - Honors and grants, 1990s (Box 1)
  - Duke appl. and CV's, Fall 2004 (Box 1)
  - Women in European history, 2003 (Box 1)
  - Women in European history-Lesbians to WWI, 2002 (Box 1)
  - Berkshire conference on the history of women, 2005 (Box 1)
  - International interdisciplinary congress on women, July 2002 (Box 1)
  - International congress of women, 1982 (Box 1)
  - Overheads-Mexico, undated (Box 1)
  - Correspondence: John Howard, Pablo Ben, Feb 2005 (Box 1)
  - Ontario workshop-learning from the Matrix, Sept 2004 (Box 1)
  - Fulbright-Austria, 2004 (Box 1)
  - Women's world in Seoul Korea, June 2005 (Box 1)
  - The Berkshire conference in Scripps College, 2005 (Box 1)
  - Abingdon, Sept 1984 (Box 1)
  - MM's paper-Anatomy of difference: toward a classification of feminist theory, undated (Box 1)
  - SAR review-Arnow and Lewis (Box 1)
  - LeGuin, 1985-1986 (Box 1)
  - The bread and roses traveling companion (Box 1)
  - Notes on Colleagues' work, 1988 (Box 1)
  - Fellowship Appalachian, 1985-1986 (Box 1)
  - SIGNS revision, 1989 (Box 1)
  - MM's paper: Gendering the feast (Box 1)
  - Lessing, walking on the shade-review, 1997 (Box 1)
  - Genus, Jan 2002 (Box 1)
  - Fredrika Bremer and the writing of America, June 1999 (Box 1)
  - PARNASS, 2000 (Box 1)
  - UU-Schuummer and MM, June 2008 (Box 1)
  - Berks UMinn, 2008 (Box 1)
  - Research Funding Application, 2006-2007 (Box 2)
  - Bremer paper and overheads, 1999 (Box 2)
  - St.Luke's-MDG, 2007 (Box 2)
  - Åbo Akademi University talk, May 2006 (Box 2)
  - Oxford women history network conference, Sept 2009 (Box 2)
  - Finland correspondence, 2001 (Box 2)
  - Wuolijoki's Ms trans from German, 2000 (Box 2)
  - Italy-Florence conference, Oct 2003 (Box 2)
  - Italy-Helena's papers, 2003 (Box 2)
  - Italy-Wuolijoki paper, 2003 (Box 2)
  - The Matilda Joslyn Gage Foundation, Dec 2009 (Box 2)
  - Norway/Iceland international women achieves, 1998 (Box 2)
  - L 'Homme 2FG, 2003-2004 (Box 2)
  - WW05-South Korea, 2005 (Box 2)
  - Overheads-Seneca Falls talk NWSA, 1998 (Box 2)
  - Humanities Lecture series, Aug 1998 (Box 2)
  - Earlier work, 1960s-1980s (Box 2)
  - Keats Thesis-music, 1964 (Box 2)
  - Camus, 1960s-1970s (Box 2)
  - Phil Novel, 1960s (Box 2)
  - Camus, Buber-sr.thesis, 1963 (Box 2)
  - Buber's "situation ethics", Winter 1968 (Box 2)
  - Martin Buber: the life of dialogue, May 1963 (Box 2)
  - Music paper, 1968 (Box 2)
  - Letters for Shadow N., 1980s (Box 2)
  - Women's studies newsletter article, 1974-1975 (Box 2)
  - Clark, 1966 (Box 2)
  - Durrell papers, 1967-1968 (Box 2)
  - Musil Materials, 1968 (Box 2)
  - Emory University, 1966-1974 (Box 2)
  - Europe trip, 1985 (Box 2)
  - Southern History Association, Nov 1988 (Box 2)
  - UW-Milwallkee appl., 1988-1989 (Box 2)
  - Travel to collections grant, 1986-1987 (Box 2)
  - Job applications, 1987-1988 (Box 2)
  - Sacramento state materials, 1986-1987 (Box 2)
  - Salem-turtle beach, 1980s (Box 2)
  - WS Colloq., 1982 (Box 2)
  - London WL mewsletter (Box 2)
  - Women's studies international forum, 1981-1982 (Box 2)
  - PARIS, 1982 (Box 2)
  - Clippings, 1970s (Box 2)
  - Haifa article, 1982 (Box 2)
  - Fr.women winters-E.Marks, 1982 (Box 2)
  - New Harmony Indiana, 1980s (Box 2)
  - Anne Morrow Lindbergh (Box 2)
  - Colette, n.d. (Box 2)
  - UW-Milwaukee letters, Fall 1982 (Box 2)
  - Feminism in West Germany, 1978 (Box 2)
  - Reflections on a journey for peace, Oct/Nov 1982 (Box 3)
  - Women of power, Fall 1991 (Box 3)
  - WS speech-Now, 1978 (Box 3)
  - France's Feminine Theory-Cixous, etc., 1974-1981 (Box 3)
  - UW correspondence, 1978-1982 (Box 3)
  - Feminist pedagogy study group, 1976-1982 (Box 3)
  - Women of the left bank-Salem, 1987 (Box 3)
  - Correspondence, 1982 (Box 3)
  - Women study-English, 1980s (Box 3)
  - Leave-Feminist Theory Europe Info, 1978-1982 (Box 3)
  - WS in Europe-presentations, 1982-1984 (Box 3)
  - NEH summer seminar, 1986 (Box 3)
  - Committee on LGBT History, Fall 2011 (Box 3)
  - Generations: exploring race, sexuality and labor across time and space, June 2011 (Box 3)
  - Feminist fellow travelers, 1985-1986 (Box 3)
  - 19th Century women travelers papers, 1990 (Box 3)
  - SCWH-Women travelers paper, 1991 (Box 3)
  - Harriet Taylor Mill, n.d. (Box 3)
  - Theresa Pulszky, n.d. (Box 3)
  - Institutional Modernization and Feminism in Greece, 1982-1987 (Box 3)
  - Gacon Dufour, 1982-1985 (Box 3)
  - Flora Tristan, 1978 (Box 3)
  - Zoe Gatti de Gamond, 1984 (Box 3)
  - Ednah Dow Cheney, n.d. (Box 3)
  - Caroline Wells Healey Dall, n.d. (Box 3)
  - Helen English Branner Fund, 1984, 1987 (Box 3)
  - Salem-MMG, 1974-1975 (Box 3)
  - Hard Scrabble, 1970s (Box 3)
  - Fannie/Eckstorm, 1970s (Box 3)
  - Unheard Melodies: Three Settings for "La Belle Dame Sans Merci", Feb 1965 (Box 3)
  - Sin Fronteras: Women's histories, global conversation, June 2005 (Box 3)
  - Miscellaneous correspondence (name cards) (Box 3)
  - Miscellaneous correspondence (post card), 2005, 2008, n.d. (Box 3)
  - Miscellaneous correspondence (letter: 1 of 3), 1982-1985 (Box 3)
  - Miscellaneous correspondence (letter: 2 of 3), 1986-1989 (Box 3)
  - Miscellaneous correspondence (letter: 3 of 3), 1999-2013, n.d. (Box 3)
  - Dillard, 1980s (Box 3)
  - Salem Critiques-MMG, 1970s (Box 3)
  - Salem annual contributor, 1970s (Box 3)
  - Women studies by Waage, 1980s (Box 3)
  - Olive Thorne Miller, n.d. (Box 3)
  - Waage materials, 1979 (Box 3)
  - Old dominion projects, 1970s (Box 4)
  - Women's studies newsletter article, 1976 (Box 4)
  - Wilma Dykeman, 1970s (Box 4)
  - Louise Dickinson Rich (Box 4)
  - Hazel Heckman, 1979 (Box 4)
  - Josephine Johnson, 1979 (Box 4)
  - Fannie Hardy Eckstorm, n.d. (Box 4)
  - Sally Carrighar file, 1970s (Box 4)
  - Frederick Ungar Publishing Co, Inc., 1977-1978 (Box 4)
  - Women Writers, 1976 (Box 4)
  - Women studies-old dominion university, 1970s (Box 4)
  - Post-tenure review (1 of 2), April 2005 (Box 4)
  - Post-tenure review (2 of 2), April 2005 (Box 4)
  - Essay index reprint series (Box 4)
  - Archives to Duke, 2003 (Box 4)
  - NWSA Journal, 2000, 2002 (Box 4)
  - Book plate-business card design, n.d. (Box 4)
  - Video copyrights-for Austria, 2003 (Box 4)
  - Christmas trip, Dec 2003 (Box 4)
  - Christmas letter, 2003 (Box 4)
  - OCSA, 2004 (Box 4)
  - The women's review of books, April 2004 (Box 4)
  - Miscellaneous correspondence (post cards) (Box 4)
  - European documentation (1 of 2), 2007 (Box 4)
  - European documentation (2 of 2), 2007 (Box 4)
  - Kalendar (calendar), 2000 (Box 4)